华仔  吃慢点
Howie, slow down.
不行
I can't.
手术之前12小时都不能吃东西
I'm not allowed to eat for 12 hours before my surgery,
我只剩两分钟了
and I only got two more minutes.
你也要动什么手术吗
What surgery are you having?
我是压力型暴饮暴食
I'm stress eating.
我最好的朋友明天要去结扎了
My best friend's getting a vasectomy tomorrow.
你是难过自己再也没机会怀他宝宝吗
And you're sad you won't be able to bear his child?
我的天
Oh, my goodness.
如果是"结扎手术失误"视频集锦
If it's "Vasectomy gone wrong" videos,
他已经全部看过了
he's seen them all.
包括一个男人看起来像坐在哈密瓜上
Including the one of the guy who's sitting
但其实是他自己血肿蛋蛋的那个视频
on what appears to be a cantaloupe but is not.
我不吃了
And I'm done.
他们要重新开拍《质子教授科学秀》节目了
They're going to start making Professor Proton's science show again.
我还以为他已经过世了
I thought he passed away.
没错
He did.
儿童科学节目常有的科学小实验  水中加入几勺苏打粉  再加一点白醋能像火山爆发
他火化后  骨灰都投进了小苏打火山里了
He was cremated, and his remains were put in a baking soda volcano.
别乱开玩笑  他对谢尔顿意义重大
Don't make jokes. He meant a lot to Sheldon.
我也一样  我是看着他节目长大的
Oh, me, too. I grew up watching his show.
他是我成为科学家的原因之一
He's one of the reasons I became a scientist.
我还以为你是为了把妹呢
Thought you did it just to get girls.
哈哈  我不是把到你了吗
Joke's on you. It worked.
他们找到接班人了吗
Have they found anyone to replace him?
不  还没有  这可不简单
No, not yet, and it won't be easy.
亚瑟·杰弗里斯是一个成就颇丰的科学家
Arthur Jeffries was an accomplished scientist.
你知道谁可以演好质子教授吗
You know who'd make a great Professor Proton?
影后梅丽尔·斯特里普
Meryl Streep.
她不是科学家
She's not a scientist.
那你告诉我
Uh, then explain to me why
为什么她和每个人都能产生化学反应
she has chemistry with literally everyone.
如果他们能让女演员来演也不错
It would be nice if they cast a woman.
新版《神秘博士》和《捉鬼特工队》的主角都是女性
你们已经有了《神秘博士》和《捉鬼特工队》
Oh, you've already got Doctor Who and the Ghostbusters.
给我们男人剩点吧
Leave us something.
你觉得应该让谁演
Who do you think it should be?
应该选一个我敬重的科学家
Well, it should be a scientist I respect.
一个声线悦耳动听
You know, someone with a pleasing voice
五官均匀对称的人
and symmetrical facial features.
他是在说他自己吗
Is he talking about himself?
他说话时  都是在说自己
If he's talking, he's talking about himself.
我只知道质子教授在我小时候触碰了我心
I just know how much Professor Proton touched me as a child,
我觉得我应该还他这份情
and I feel that I owe it to him
也该像他那样去"触碰"更多孩子
to try and touch as many children as possible.
你该把这句话放进试镜视频里
You should put that on your audition tape.
第十一季  第六集
你还好吗
You doing okay?
不  人家紧张死了
No, I'm very nervous.
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
礼品店
Gift shop.
这里没有礼品店  给我坐下
There is no gift shop. Sit down.
这也是你自己的主意啊
This was your idea.
滚床单也是我的主意  你看看后果多严重
So was having sex, and look where that got us.
这没什么大不了的  别唧歪了
This isn't a big deal. Stop whining.
你生娃时我也说过同样的话  结果你踹了我
When you were in labor and I said that, you kicked me.
霍沃德··沃罗威茨
Howard Wolowitz?
-要我陪你进去吗  -不用
- Want me to go with you? - No.
-我没事  -对啊  我俩可以的
- I'll be fine. - Yeah, we got this.
给我坐下
Sit down!
祝我好运吧
Wish me luck.
走错方向了  小子
Other way, buster.
你准备好了吗
Okay, you ready?
差不多了
Yeah, almost.
我正在练习我的面部表情
I'm working on my facial expressions.
看  这是我燃起兴致的表情
See, uh, I've got interested.
这是兴致高昂的表情
I've got very interested.
暴怒的表情
Enraged.
你怎么会暴怒呢
Why would you be enraged?
准备要万全  平日多烧香
Hmm. Better to have it and not need it
好过临时抱佛脚
than to need it and not have it.
好吧
Okay.
准备...
And...
开拍
rolling.
大家好  我是理论物理学家  谢尔顿·库珀博士
Hello. I am theoretical physicist, Dr. Sheldon Cooper,
为质子博士一角试镜
auditioning for the role of Professor Proton.
现在  请允许我进入角色
Now, excuse me while I get into character.
大家好  我是质子教授
Hello. I am Professor Proton.
今天  孩子们
And today, boys and girls,
我们要一起进入有趣的科学世界
we're going to have fun with science.
你知道可以用手边的家庭用品
Did you know you could calculate the mass of an electron
计算出电子的质量吗  真的可以呢
using household items? It's true.
你只需要一支铅笔  一些纸
All you'll need is a pencil, some paper,
干冰  外用酒精
dry ice, rubbing alcohol,
和一卷50微米细的钴60线轴
and a spool of 50-micron-thick cobalt-60 wire.
要记得  别把线轴放进嘴里
And, remember, don't put it in your mouth,
不然你没变成科学家
or instead of becoming a scientist,
就先变成放射狂人了
you'll become wildly radioactive.
等一下  我有个问题
Hang on. I have a question.
你有其他没有致命危险的实验吗
Do you have any experiments that aren't life-threatening?
不是吧  人家拍得好好的  全被你毁了
Come on! That was a perfect take, and you ruined it.
你看  我暴怒的表情用上了
Oh, look! Hey, I did need enraged.
-看来真的很痛啊  -不痛
- Really hurts, huh? - No.
他只是在说"哎哟  这价格太划算了"
He's just saying, "Ow can these prices be so low""
别担心  只需休息一两天就好
It's gonna be okay. A day or two of rest,
你会好起来的
and you'll be fine.
那你真是不懂戏精犹太人了
You know nothing about Jewish people.
我去看看她
Um, let me go check on her.
好了  现在有一点小尴尬了
Okay, uh, this is a bit awkward.
手册上写我需要检查一下手术部位的
It says here that I need to check the area
发红和肿胀情况
for redness and swelling.
我已经痛到麻木了  随你便吧
You know what? It hurts so much, go ahead.
所以孩子们
So you see, boys and girls,
H  也就是螺旋性  是使用相对论的自然变量
H, or helicity, is the natural variable to use relativistically
S·P  再除以P的量
is defined as S dot P, divided by the magnitude of P.
所以下次如果操场上有人告诉你
So the next time someone on the playground tells you
你只能用整数值来
you can only use integral values for the matrix
决定反质子的自旋
that determines the spin of the antiproton,
别和那孩子做朋友
you stop being friends with that kid,
因为他肯定成不了材
'cause he's going nowhere.
我们下周再会  质子教授跟大家说
Until next week, this is Professor Proton saying,
010000100111100101100101
是美国信息交换标准代码二进制数的"拜"
That's "Bye" in ASCII binary,
"二"个拜  拜拜
or good-binary.
你们觉得如何呢
So, what do you think?
我已经跟他说我觉得超赞了
Well, I already told him that I loved it,
但如果你们有人觉得说得太绕  太危险...
but if you found it confusing or dangerous or--
或我随便举例  比如超长了几倍时间
I don't know-- three to four times too long,
现在就可以提出你们的意见
now is the time to share.
我不知道说什么
I... I don't know what to say.
莱纳德  你有什么想说的吗
Leonard, do you know what to say?
谢尔顿  我觉得呢...
Sheldon, uh, I thought it, uh...
感觉视频中的你  玩得很开心
It-it looked like you were having so much fun.
你以前也教过我用这话应付佩妮
That's what you used to tell me to say to Penny
就在看完她难看的表演后教的
after one of her terrible plays.
所以问题出在哪呢
Well, what was wrong with it?
你们会觉得...
You know, did you find it...
快接近神经病了吗
borderline psychotic?
我个人觉得呢
I mean,
我挺喜欢这一点  但...
I liked that about it, but...
请畅所欲言
you guys discuss.
你还记得你小时候
Do you remember when you were a kid
看质子教授的节目吗
and you'd watch Professor Proton?
当然啊
Of course.
那他有过让你觉得...  比方说...
Well, did he ever make you-- I don't know--
痛恨科学与搞科学的人吗
hate science and the people who do it?
你什么意思
What are you saying?
我觉得你要想改进
I-I just think it would be... better
那你对儿童的不屑
if your contempt for children
就不能够这么堂而皇之
wasn't so much in the foreground.
你是要我说谎吗
Well, you want me to lie?
这不是说谎  是演戏啊
Well, it's not lying-- it's acting.
虽然谢尔顿·库珀不爱小孩子
Sheldon Cooper may not like kids,
但质子教授很喜欢孩子啊
but Professor Proton loves them.
有意思
Interesting.
我还没用这角度想过呢
You know, I hadn't really thought of it that way.
这就像是我本人很怕狗
It-It's similar to how I'm afraid of dogs,
但我桌游里的角色很喜欢狗一样
but my D&D character likes dogs, you know?
但他对狗过敏  所以不能接近狗狗
But he's allergic, so he can't be around them.
我们为什么还不养狗
Why don't we have a dog?
你可以重拍一个啊
Hey, you can always reshoot it.
也是啦
Mm, I suppose.
或许这次我还能去请教
And, you know, maybe I could even get some tips
有过专业演员经历的人
from someone who's acted professionally.
谢尔顿  我当然很乐意帮助你啦
Sheldon, obviously, I'd be happy to help you out.
我无言以对
I don't know what to say.
谢尔顿  怎么了
Hey, Sheldon. What's up?
我需要一个演戏教练
I need an acting coach.
知名杰出英国演员  也曾出演过《星际旅行:  初代》
你能给我帕特里克·斯图尔特的电话吗
Would you give me Patrick Stewart's number?
不能
No.
好吧  你来教也行
Fine. I guess you can do it.
妮妮
Bernie?
你从哪弄来的铃
Where did you get a bell?
应用商店
App store.
真好玩  让我看看
Fun. Let me see.
等你能抓到我了再还你手机
When you catch me, you can have it back.
你想躺下一起看个电影吗
You want to lie down, watch a movie?
不行  我得去做第16周的产检
I can't. I got my 16-week checkup to get to,
完事后我会买中餐外卖回来当晚饭
and then I'll pick up some Chinese for dinner.
我会把哈雷带上
I'll take Halley with me.
你确定你这样不会太累吗
You-you sure you're not overdoing it?
-没事  不会的  -那太好了
- No, it's fine. - Great.
那不如别买中餐
Then maybe, instead of Chinese,
去把烤架热了  弄几块牛排如何
fire up the grill and throw on a couple of steaks?
宫保鸡丁  谢谢老婆大人
Kung pao chicken, please.
-惨了  -怎么了
- Oh, boy. - What?
他们选出新的质子教授演员了
They cast the new Professor Proton.
是谢尔顿吗
Is it Sheldon?
不是
Not exactly.
惠顿
Wheaton!
是威尔·惠顿
It's Wil Wheaton.
医生怎么说
How was the doctor?
一切良好  但我有个事情要说
Good, but I have some news.
别说是双胞胎  别是双胞胎
Don't say twins. Don't say twins. Don't say twins.
别说是双胞胎啊
Don't say twins.
不是双胞胎
It's not twins.
我是说  我一定会超爱他们啦
Oh. I mean, because I would have loved them both.
医生说我操劳过度
The doctor said I was overdoing it,
让我在床上歇着保胎
so she put me on bed rest just to be safe.
太心疼了
Oh, no.
虽然看起来不像  但我正在朝你飞奔而去
It may not look like it, but I'm running to you!
亚瑟  你好啊
Hello, Arthur.
"安息"这两个字
What-what part of "Rest in peace"
你是有哪个字不懂
don't you understand?
我猜你会来是因为你听到消息了吧
I suppose you're here because you heard the news?
谢尔顿  我是从你的想象中虚构出来的
Sheldon, I'm a figment of your imagination.
不是老子听到什么消息
I don't hear news.
真是个暴躁的虚构体
You're a grumpy figment.
是这样的  他们要重启你的节目
Look, they're remaking your show,
他们选了威尔·惠顿来当质子教授
and they cast Wil Wheaton as Professor Proton.
而最糟的地方就是  他都不是科学家
And the worst part is, he's not even a scientist.
不  最糟的地方是
No, the-the worst part is,
我坐在湿哒哒的木头上
I'm sitting on a moist log.
我们得阻止这一切  保护你名声
We have to stop this and protect your legacy.
有个毛名声啊
What legacy?
我节目最后两季
My-my last two seasons,
档期是在周日早上五点半播出
I was on Sunday morningn at 5:30.
收视率还被陶土儿童节目给打败
We-we were beat by Davey and Goliath.
我真不敢相信你都不在乎
I can't believe you don't care.
相信吧
Believe it.
但我在乎  非常在乎
Well, I care, a lot,
威尔·惠顿绝对会后悔认识我
and Wil Wheaton will rue the day he ever met me.
我觉得大多数人都这么觉得
I think that's true of most people.
你们好啊
Hi, guys.
就想过来看看你们俩怎么样了
Wanted to check in and see how you two were doing.
我们挺好
We're okay.
对啊  跟我老婆赖在床上
Yeah, hanging out in bed with my wife,
用裤裆内的体温给冻豆子化冻
thawing out some frozen peas in my pants--
宛如梦中啊
living the dream.
我去哄她吧
Oh, I'll get her.
我以为拉杰会来帮手呢
I thought Raj was helping you out.
没来  他得上班
No, he had to work.
再说了  关于印度仆人的玩笑
Plus, he has a quota for the amount of
他的容忍是有限的
Indian servant jokes he can tolerate,
而我貌似已经把额度用完了
and, apparently, I filled it.
你歇着吧  我可以去哄她
Well, you're... I can get the baby.
不用了  华仔可以的  他能行
No, Howie's got it. He's fine.
对吧  华仔
Right, Howie?
比什么时候都行
Never better.
别傻了
Don't be silly.
我可以请假帮你们照看哈雷
I'll take the rest of the day off and watch Halley for you.
或者我们可以打给斯图尔特
Or we can call Stuart.
我敢说他肯定会马上关店
I'm sure he could close up the store,
跳上公交车  飞奔来这里
hop on a bus, and be here in no time.
他的确很爱公交车
He does love the bus.
等下
Okay, hang on.
你俩是不相信我可以照看好你们的娃吗
Do you guys not trust me to take care of your baby?
-当然不是  -不是不是
- No. - No!
-不是  -真不是
- No. - No.
我觉得还是...
So I-I guess...
不行
no.
不是我们不信任你  只是...
It's not that we don't trust you-- it's just...
你看起来不太像是喜欢小娃娃的人
you don't seem like much of a baby person.
我能照看好你们的傻逼娃娃  好吗
I can watch your stupid baby, okay?
如果她哭了  我会抱她起来
If she cries, I will pick her up.
如果她饿了  我会给她热奶
If she's hungry, I'll give her a bottle.
如果她拉粑粑了  我会点上熏香
And if she poops, I'll light some incense.
那可真是帮了大忙了
It would be a big help.
好吧  谢谢你
Okay. Thank you.
相信我  你们俩绝对可以放一百个心
Trust me, you guys have nothing to worry about.
当年在我们老家
You know, back in Nebraska,
我们家的小猪仔
I raised all our baby pigs
都是我一手养大到可以送去宰了
right until the day they were slaughtered.
所以除非你们娃是早餐肉做的
So, unless your baby's made of breakfast meat,
否则她好着呢
she's fine.
你有天会去做结扎手术吗
Would you ever get a vasectomy?
或许你没有注意到
Uh, in case you haven't noticed,
印度人不是很喜欢计划生育
Indians aren't too big on birth control.
很可能从我们开始这话题到现在
There's probably, like, a million more of us
印度又多了一百万人口
since we started this conversation.
你还好吧
You okay?
不好
No.
网上所有关于威尔的评论
No, all these comments online about Wil,
一水儿全是支持和好话
they're nothing but supportive and kind.
那个毒舌刻薄的互联网哪去了
Where's the mean, snarky Internet
怎么每次我剪完头发它就出现呢
that shows up every time I get a haircut?
你知道毒舌刻薄的是我们  对吧
You know that's us, right?
幸运的是  我搞到了那家
Well, luckily, I got the number of the company
试图重启这节目公司的电话
who's trying to reboot the show,
所以我需要你们都打去表达你们的不满
so I need you all to call and register your displeasure.
谢尔顿  没人会这么做
Sheldon, no one's gonna do that.
有哦
Not true.
我知道已经有三个人打去表达不满了
I know of three calls they've received already:
一位是南方绅士
a-a Southern gentleman,
一位是伦敦烟囱清扫工
um, a Cockney chimney sweep,
还有一位是
and, uh,
T先生
Mr. T, hmm?
这位先生  剧透一下
Who-- spoiler alert--
可怜那位试图重启这节目的傻瓜
pities the fool who tries to reboot that show.
那个发型糟糕的无聊疯子呢
What about tiresome lunatic with a bad haircut?
他怎么没打去
Has he called yet?
拜托
Come on.
多少次我们团结起来
How many times have we banded together
一起去拯救我们热爱的节目
to try to save a show that we loved?
这次我们改变套路  把这节目扼杀在摇篮中
L-Let's shake things up and try to kill one.
有个能让孩子喜欢科学的节目
Isn't the important thing that there's a show
难道不重要吗
to get kids excited about science?
谁在乎小孩和他们喜欢什么啊
Who cares about kids and what they like?
这事关我
This is about me
和我还是个孩子时喜欢的节目
and something I liked when-when I was a kid.
万一节目重启很成功呢
What if the reboot is great?
那就更糟了
That's even worse.
如果我喜欢它
If-if I like it,
感觉就像背叛了亚瑟
I'll feel like I'm being disloyal to Arthur.
他是我的导师和朋友
He was a mentor and a friend,
我不会为了好莱坞某个帅哥  比如威尔·惠顿
and I won't toss him aside for some Hollywood pretty boy
而抛弃他
like Wil Wheaton.
他的话很难反驳啊
It's hard to argue with him.
因为他根本不讲理吗  的确是
Because he makes no sense? Yeah.
这感觉其实挺好的
This is actually kind of nice,
你我有机会一起在床上赖几天
you and me getting to spend a couple days in bed together.
是啊  很快我们家
Yeah. Pretty soon, we're gonna have
就会有两个哇哇叫的宝宝了
two crying babies in the house.
我很高兴我蛋疼  因为全是它们的错
I'm glad my balls hurt. It's all their fault.
让我们一起享受这宁静的时光
Well, let's just enjoy this quiet time
趁现在还有机会
while we still got it.
是啊
Yeah.
但这也太安静了吧
Yeah, it is really quiet.
你觉得佩妮能应付得来吗
You think Penny's doing okay?
佩妮  一切还好吗
Penny, everything all right?!
一切都好
Hey. All good.
往她奶嘴上沾了点酒  她立马昏睡过去了
Dipped her pacifier in a little bourbon, she conked right out.
希望你是在开玩笑
I hope you're joking.
当然是开玩笑啊  我才不会分享我的酒呢
Of course I'm joking. I don't share my bourbon.
她在开玩笑
She's joking.
肯定是
Definitely.
应该吧
Probably.
威尔·惠顿  威尔·惠顿
Wil Wheaton. Wil Wheaton.
对了  我是谢尔顿
This is Sheldon, by the way.
谢尔顿
Hi, Sheldon.
给  我在你的栅栏发现这张披萨传单
Here, I found this pizza flyer in your fence.
谢谢
Thank you.
现在你欠我个人情
Okay, now you owe me a favor.
你去拒演质子教授
Turn down the role of Professor Proton.
我不同意
I don't think so.
你不能当质子教授  你又不是科学家
You can't be Professor Proton. You're not a scientist.
我也从没上过太空星舰
Well, I was never on a starship,
但假装自己上过让我买下了这栋房子
but pretending I was bought me this house.
要是我假装的时间更久
And if I'd pretended a little longer,
还能买下带泳池的房子呢
it would have a swimming pool.
有些东西就不该被重启
Some things shouldn't be rebooted.
有些东西本来就很完美了
Some things were perfect the way they were.
比如有城墙的约克  非常美好
Like the walled city of York-- it was a delight.
但新约克[纽约]  算了吧
But New York? Blech.
你有没想过  如果亚瑟得知他的节目比他还长寿
Did you ever consider that maybe Arthur would be happy to know
会很高兴呢
that his show has outlived him?
我深表怀疑
I doubt it.
他是个刻薄暴躁的臭老头
He was kind of a mean old crank.
谢尔顿  我保证我会努力把节目做好
Sheldon, I promise that I will work my hardest to make this show great
好让新一代的孩子们
so that a whole new generation of kids
长大后会说
will grow up and they will be able to say
是质子教授让他们投身科学领域
that Professor Proton was the reason they got into science.
这番话很有说服力
That was very persuasive.
谢谢
Thanks.
但我不会被你的演技
But I won't be seduced by your acting skills
或电影明星魅力所诱惑
nor your movie star charisma.
质子教授只有一个
There's only one Professor Proton,
而他绝没有上述两种特质
and he had neither of those things.
我再给你一次机会退出
I'll give you one more chance to bow out.
不然怎样
Or what?
我们初次见面时  你我是敌人
When we first met, we were enemies,
但我们解决了矛盾  成为了朋友
but we worked through that and we became friends.
你真想回到当初吗
Do you really want to go back?
老实说  感觉没什么不同
Honestly, it doesn't feel very different.
我不会走的
I'm not leaving!
好吧  那我就放狗出来咬你
All right, I'm gonna sic my dog on you.
你又没有养狗
You don't have a dog.
有的
Yes, I do.
我分辨不出你是否在说谎
Ugh, I can't tell if you're lying--
你演技太高超了
you're such a good actor!
你好吗
Hey, how you doing?
你怎么来了
What are you doing here?
我就顺路过来看看
Oh, I just came by, you know,
看你是否需要帮忙
to see if you need any help.
霍华德和伯纳黛特派你来监督我
Howard and Bernadette asked you to check up on me.
这话不全对
That is not entirely true.
还有莱纳德和  所有人
So did Leonard and... everybody.
你们是觉得我有多不负责任啊
How irresponsible do you all think I am?
我们不觉得你不负责任啊
We don't think you're irresponsible.
我们只是觉得你...
We think you're...
喜爱玩耍
fun-loving.
这只是"不负责任"好听一点的说法
That is just a nice word for "Irresponsible."
看来你比我们想的要机智
You might be more on the ball than we thought.
我有点饿了
I'm getting a little hungry.
这次我来吧
Want me to get it this time?
那再好不过了
That'd be great.
真好玩
This is fun.
你也能看到一个气鼓鼓的金发妞走进来
And now you also get to see an annoyed blonde walk into the room.
干嘛
What?
能给我们拿点零食吗
Can you get us a little snack?
不叫你们的间谍去拿吗
You sure you don't want your spy to do it?
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
你们真的很不信任我  还让艾米过来看看
You really don't trust me? You had to have Amy stop by?
-我们信任你  -是啊
- We trust you. - Yeah.
你是个糟糕的服务员
You were a terrible waitress,
我们还是叫你给我们拿零食了啊
and we still asked you to get us a snack.
失陪一下  我要去照顾你们的宝宝
Excuse me while I go take care of your baby.
然后我会拿零食给你们
Then I'll bring you your snack,
到时你们就可以继续羞辱我了
and you can insult me some more.
不知道你怎么想
I don't know about you,
但我绝对不会吃她送来的食物
but I am not eating whatever she brings us.
哈雷  没事的
Hey, Halley. Aw, it's okay.
佩妮阿姨来了  我帮你换尿布
Auntie Penny's here. Shh. Let's get you changed.
你爸妈说他们相信我
Your mommy and daddy say they trust me,
但他们满嘴都是你尿布里现在包着的东西
but they're full of the same stuff your diaper is.
这下我内疚了
Now I feel bad.
反正她从没喜欢过我
Well, she never really liked me.
现在她也讨厌你  感觉还不赖
It's kind of nice she hates you now, too.
但你有我呢
Aw, but I'm here for you,
我不会让你受到任何伤害
and I would never let anything happen to you,
因为佩妮阿姨真的好爱好爱你
because your Auntie Penny loves you so much.
妈妈
Mama.
那是她第一个词吗
Was that her first word?
妈妈
Mama.
不不  宝宝  我不是你妈妈
Uh, no. No, baby. I'm not your mama.
你妈妈是我们现在要去见的那位善良女士
Your mama's the nice lady we're gonna go see right now
这样我就能在她面前嘚瑟啦
so I can rub this in her face.
听见了吗  你俩贱人
Do you hear that, suckers?
她叫我妈妈
She called me Mama!
你好  亚瑟
Hello, Arthur.
你知道
You-you know,
我们  我们也可以在熟食店见面的
we could... we could also meet in-in a deli.
很抱歉告诉你  我辜负了你
I'm sorry to say that I failed you.
我试过阻止威尔·惠顿出演质子教授
I tried to stop Wil Wheaton being Professor Proton,
但我没能做到
but I couldn't.
知道吗  这种事情
See, now, that's-that's the kind of thing
很适合边吃熏牛肉三明治
you could tell a fella over a...
边告诉对方的
pastrami sandwich.
别担心
Well, don't worry.
现在他会永远在我的仇家名单里
He's now on my enemies list forever.
我跟他永世绝交
He's totally cut off.
有意思
Interesting.
其他人能去哪登记上那份名单呢
Can-can anyone sign-sign up for that list?